worldsave.net 2017-10-10

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains you how we use personal information collected at [Alternative Energy](http://www.worldsave.net/) site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here.

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you.

**Information Collected**  
We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.

**Information Use**  
We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files- “ _cookies_ ” – that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

We also use third party advertising companies to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information which includes only your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. Your name, address, email address, or telephone number is NOT included.

**DoubleCLick Dart Cookie.** Google as our main third party ad vendor uses the DoubleCLick Dart Cookie technology to best serve you the most relevant ads about goods and services that may suit your interest and enhance your surfing experience. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). You may also opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Disclosing Information**  
We do not share your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

**Changes to this Policy**  
Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please contact us via our [**Contact Page**](http://www.worldsave.net/inquire/). You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details form any list under our control.
